大家好
我是小舞
今天和大家一同观赏的是
2015年马来西亚公开赛男单1/4决赛
由中国选手陈龙
对阵日本选手桃田贤斗
第一局二比一
龙哥控网抢攻得分
You know it's tough
Physically
It's too
两平跑腿转身往前跟进
龙哥快推拉开逃
劈掉斜线
龙哥回放逃反推转身放远网抓推
回放中路连续推转身
抓摆脱下压
You know they started coding well
抓摆脱正手突击直线得分
I don't know the through in the same way
三平豪推正手龙哥蓝调好反推
转身往前跟进
龙快推拉开淘下压
往前抢
放龙哥推挑过顶逼摆脱劈杀斜线得分
We you know we we talked a lot about in the
last match about the confidence at this and5比三
双方网前较量
龙哥推挑过顶
往前分对角陶推挑正手往前跟进
龙哥空头顶
双方往前较量逃快推拉开龙哥抽压回放
逃往前高质量分斜线得分四比五
龙哥连续控正
手抓过度
头顶突击斜线得分六比四
龙哥抓推
双方网前较量好快推拉开龙哥过度
中路放网逃空往下压
Throughout the event
推头顶
龙哥下压逃往前分斜线
龙哥被动回搓好空往下压
飞头顶龙哥高质量反拍斜线蓝调得分
I think this is a really interesting match
I've been looking forward to this one
I think i want to see what mamotor
Can come up with tactically
Canny break chan
L's game
六比七
龙哥停顿分斜线
好反推
转身往前分斜线
龙哥回勾掏空
往下压
龙哥抓推突击得分
八比六淘推正手控网抢攻
推头顶龙哥滑板斜线控网下压
上网高质量回放得分
Nine six
Yeah
Chen
Long is just asking for the court to be mopped their hands
Went down
七比九龙哥推头顶朝下压
双方网前较量
掏空网抢攻
往前跟进
龙哥回勾
侧身突击一拍回放中路推
正手抓过渡
正手突击斜线得分
Nice flick off the ne
八比九桃发后场双方斗网
头顶突击一拍控
头顶朝下压
双方往前较量
连续推转身
抓过度抢搓龙哥
快推拉开控正手
龙哥回放桃连续控正手
滑板打重心调动控网逃高质量劈掉斜线得分
九平
龙哥推挑过顶逃抽压
龙哥回放网前抓扑得分
十比九逃推挑正手往前分斜线
双方往前较量
推头顶抓
摆脱下压逃网前对角变化
龙哥回放下压推
转身抓摆脱头顶突击斜线得分
Now the advantage to chan
Long uh
The big game mental it
Just two points in it
Yeah
This is interesting being left hand is about that
12比十
陶连续空转身
网前跟进
龙哥控网抢攻得分
Yeah
There you're right
13比十逃控网
龙哥反控转身往前逼压
往前分斜线逃回搓抓推拦截得分
14比11逃控网杀
上网连贯得分
Good smash
Goodness me
How did he dig that out of his chest
It's the change and then real speed to get in behind it
Look at that fully committed great plane
13比14龙抢放逃
快推拉开
往前扑压
龙哥反打空挡
转主动控网抢攻得分
16比13
陶抢放龙哥反推转身
双方网前较量机会不好
陶选择过度
后场龙哥下压往前跟进逃反推转身
双方网前较量
陶推挑正手往前跟进
龙回放
陶推挑正手过渡
后场抓过度抢搓龙哥放远网抓推得分
It's really has just gone up
Almost imperceptible the level
But real quality
17比13
陶推挑正手
双方网前较量
陶推挑过顶
龙哥抽压逃抓推拦截
双方网前较量
逃反推转身
龙哥反拍过渡
后场斜线过渡
逃控网抢攻得分
Doing so nice
18比14陶推转身
双方网前较量
机会不好
桃先压一拍
网前高质量平推得手
19比15
龙哥发后场双方抽档较量
龙哥网前对角变化
起跳重杀得分
Uc stretching him to one side
And then the smash to the other side
Good play
16比20
随着桃田进攻出界
龙哥赢得了首局比赛的胜利
Twenty one sixteen
Twenty
One sixteen
Four minutes of flight
And as we were saying
And exactly the right time
Fourteen thirteen
第二局一比零
龙哥推转身回放好反推
正手抓过度抢放
龙哥控网抢攻得分
The line onto the line
Look at this
So quickly into position
两平双方网前较量
龙哥推转身抓
摆脱头顶点直线得分
There's a family one two
五比二豪放远网抓推龙哥接杀转对角豪回放
龙哥推正手机会不好
先压一拍
双方往前较量
龙哥下压推挑过顶
好抓过度
正手突击斜线得分
Tactically
Do do you want to play with the good end first
Or do you want to play with the good end last
六比三跑腿转身
龙哥蓝调
双方往前较量
龙哥抢放抓富得分
At the change of ends in the third more difficult
More rallies to actually win
The points
I think it was a different philosophy
七比三逃往前分斜线
龙哥推头顶朝下压双方圆网控制
双方网前较量
龙哥控网抢攻得分
八比三逃抢放龙哥快推拉开往前分
对角逃快推正手放远网
加力抽压回放
中路龙哥反控转身往前跟进下压双方网前较量
龙哥推头顶抓
摆脱头顶突击直线得分
The clear
Yeah
But thought that's trouble
Gain the it's just the precision with the smashes from chen
Long is not trying to over hit
I mean you used to be quite wild in younger days
Going for the big power smashes
Now
He's got such good control to the line
十比三操控正手放网
龙哥反控转身好反拍过渡
后场龙哥同样反拍过渡
后场抓摆脱进攻
推头顶逃下压快推正手
龙哥劈掉斜线
双方网前较量
掏空网抢攻
高质量原网转进网得分
To read his game
Very very well
Here
He's picking up everything
And it took the net cord to beat him
He was there again
Wasn't he he read the shirt
Just the net cord beat him
12比五
龙哥劈杀斜线推正手双方圆网控制
龙哥推头顶桃
高质量
头顶劈杀斜线得分
Pay off brings
The shuttle down a little bit deeper than chen long
Was expecting
六比12
龙哥推挑头顶朝下压推
转身往前分斜线机会不好逃
选择过度推球
逼摆脱头顶杀一拍
往前跟进
控网龙哥反控转身抓
摆脱头顶杀斜线得分
No through everything at him
Couldn't get through
And then chen long again
So efficient once
He did get the attack the motto
Anticipating straight chain
Long holding and going cross lovely like
七比13
双方网前较量逃抓扑得分
Oh my godness
That's well
Taken that was super play
Lovely spinning net
Stayed with it
Got the reward
See you one step pop it back
九比14
龙哥推转身回放
陶同样推转身放网
平推龙哥反顶转
主动抓摆脱进攻
往前跟进
陶推挑过顶放圆网下压
连续控正手
龙哥斜线过度投放远网抓推
龙哥高质量接杀党员网
迫使陶挑球出界
He's a little bit
Easier to redirection from there
15比九
龙哥抓推突击得分
Yeah
The problem we going around the head into position
Look at that by the time is hitting his body wa
16比九逃抢放龙哥推头顶桃下压勾对角
龙哥回搓
龙哥判断犹豫
逃放原网
龙哥反控转身控头顶抓
摆脱进攻
抢放网下压逃回放
龙哥推头顶
机会不好
龙哥选择过度掏空网抢攻
上网高质量勾对角得手
Double cross here
We go
First cross
Second cross
Lovely play
Lovely control
Say good steep angle with that forces channel
Long off balance
18比11
陶推挑头顶龙哥下压
往前跟进
逃放远网抓推龙哥
防反
往前跟进
平高压
头顶滑板掉一拍逃回放
龙哥快推
转身抓过度
往前逼压得分
Final at the malaysian open chan
Long never progressed beyond that
19比11
逃控网
龙哥推挑过顶抓摆脱
劈掉斜线得分
It's not match point opportunities
Just watch the racket head here
Slicing across the shuttle
20比11
随着陶控网抢攻出界
龙哥赢得了本场比赛的胜利
以大比分二比零战胜日本选手桃田贤斗
成功晋级2015马来西亚公开赛男单四强
Minutes of and real demonstration of
How to just up the intense
Stick up the pressure
Win's needed
Yeah
Coach will be pretty happy with that
Confirmation of the score
哈哈我知错了
Yeah
We've got huge
Talent
As mama